Follow me.
Search the city.
Yes, sir.
Sir, there is nothing here.
Move.
Next.
What are they searching for this time?
What are you looking at?
Get inside.
After him!
Go!
Halt!
This way!
General, please take a look.
So they pass messages through paintings.
Search the premises.
Yes, sir.
General Ning,
What are you doing?
General, look.
Seize him.
Yes, sir.
General,
Do not touch my paintings.
Stop!
Ning Yuanci,
on what grounds do you arrest him?
Our general
suspects he is a spy
colluding with the enemy.
This deer totem
is the evidence.
Impossible!
This is clearly Xue...
The innocent need no defense.
Lady Keying,
you need not waste your words on him.
Under the Emperor's watch,
how could I be falsely accused by him?
Chu Qingjun,
he just doesn't want
to implicate Xue Ruowan.
Take him away.
Yes.
Move.
Behave.
Bad news, Xue Ruowan.
Chu Qingyun has been captured
by Ning Yuanci.
Let's go save him.
The painting of Nirvana of the Phoenix
that Chu Qingyun restored for you,
Ning Yuanci insists
it's evidence of treason.
How could that painting
be evidence of treason?
Ning Yuanci said
there's a deer totem
on the canvas
related to Northern spies.
Was that totem
originally there?
I have no impression of it at all.
Forget it. Never mind.
Anyway, come with me
to explain it to Ning Yuanci.
Just say the painting
belongs to your mother,
and it has absolutely nothing to do
with Northern spies.
Let's go.
I won't go with you.
That painting is not my mother's.
And I never asked Chu Qingyun
to restore any painting for me.
What do you mean?
Are you going to leave him to die?
Have you figured out
what Ning Yuanci's purpose is?
I advise you not to be
so self-righteous,
lest you cause an even bigger disaster.
Me, self-righteous?
To make you look like
the strong female lead,
I had to play
the vain villainess,
and cruelly hurt Ning Yuanci,
making him mistakenly think
I liked Chu Qingyun.
That's why he's taking personal revenge.
Ultimately,
this is all because of you.
You mean
Ning Yuanci went to all this trouble
for you?
You're way too full of yourself.
You think you can just go to him,
say a few words,
and make him go soft?
Xue Keying,
to him,
you're nothing but a pawn
to be used.
Even if you're right,
what about Chu Qingyun?
He is completely innocent.
Chu Qingyun looked out for you,
yet you immediately
cut ties with him
just to save yourself.
Xue Ruowan,
you are too selfish.
And to think I saved you
time and time again.
Without me,
you would have died a hundred times over.
You did save me,
but so what?
Just because you saved me,
do I have to obey you
and live your way?
If one cannot protect oneself,
how can one protect others?
When you're in trouble,
Father protects you.
I can only protect myself.
I originally thought
you were willing to risk your life
for freedom,
and would rather die than go against
your heart.
I thought you knew better than me
how to protect the weak.
Now it seems
I thought too highly of you.
Why should I be a
perfect person?
Why must I sacrifice myself
to get everything I want?
I just need to marry Ning Yuanci
to get
endless wealth and
Father's favor.
Don't even think about stopping me.
If this is the happiness you want,
then take it.
If you won't save Chu Qingyun,
I will.
I don't have much else,
but what I despise most
is the inversion of
black and white in this world,
and good people suffering
baseless slander.
However,
I still want to advise you,
don't end up failing to save Chu Qingyun
and getting yourself killed
in the process.
You don't need to teach me
how to make choices.
This is my role.
You have your way of living,
and I have mine.
Who gave you the painting in your hand?
Who is the mastermind behind this?
Speak!
You want me to speak?
Impossible.
General,
he seems to be dead.
He won't speak.
What about you?
Do you want to end up like him?
I drew that painting
on a whim.
The image of a deer
is often used by northern tribes,
but that doesn't mean
they are the only ones
who know this totem style.
Even if you beat me to death,
I won't confess to this crime.
General,
Second Lady Xue
is asking to see you outside the manor.
Xue Keying really cares about you.
She's not afraid of death
to deliver herself to our door.
Fine,
since you won't speak...
I'll go ask her.
Don't
make things difficult for Miss Keying.
Come at me instead.
You said
the Phoenix Nirvana painting is yours.
Then tell me,
when was it painted?
And the deer totem,
was it painted before
or after?
I found the painting.
But Chu Qingyun is innocent.
Release him.
When Xue Ruowan was poisoned,
you were clearly not the murderer,
yet you insisted you did it.
Now you are risking your life
to take the blame for Chu Qingyun.
Do you enjoy
being a scapegoat so much?
I believe Chu Qingyun
is a good man.
He would never
betray his country for glory.
You once said I was a good man too.
But I am not.
I would rather kill a thousand by mistake
than let one go.
What is this?
I chopped off Chu Qingyun's hand.
He confessed everything.
That painting was done last night.
The ink isn't even dry yet.
Next time before you play the fool,
please
do your homework.
As long as I can achieve my goal,
I can sacrifice anyone.
Including you.
I had an audience with His Majesty today,
and learned
that the General has finally agreed
to fulfill the marriage contract
with Wan'er.
I am finally at ease.
Then, as His Majesty wishes,
the wedding will take place in two days.
I have heard that the General
arrested the palace painter,
Chu Qingyun.
To think he is a spy
from the Northern Frontier.
You are truly well-informed, Duke.
Indeed.
I did indeed find on Chu Qingyun...
We found a special painting
bearing the emblem
of the enemy spy organization.